http://www.carforums.net/about/privacy

Privacy Policy
This statement describes our practices with respect to visitors to CarSavvy.com (the "Site"). It
describes the extent of our responsibilities and visitors to this Site are
deemed to accept it. Please review it carefully.
At CarSavvy.com we respect your
privacy. We will use our best efforts to ensure that your information is secure
and only used for the purposes for which you have consented.
Collection of Information
CarSavvy.com only collects
personal information from you if you are listing a vehicle.  When listing a vehicle the only personal
information you are required to provide is your email address.  However, you have the option of providing
more personal information in order to provide more than one means to contact
you.
CarSavvy.com does collect
anonymous information about visitors to the Site.  This information is used internally to
perform traffic analysis.
Use of Your Information and Consent
CarSavvy.com only collects
personal information about you with your specific knowledge.  If you list
a vehicle, you are asked to provide an email address for contact purposes and
you have the option of providing telephone numbers or text messaging numbers as
additional contact information.  When you
provide us with your personal information, you consent and agree to our use and
disclosure of your personal information for the following purposes:
to provide the service you have requested, and to
operate our business, as described in this Privacy Policy;
to enable potential buyers to contact you; and
to offer you more information about our services
and the services of affiliates (If you opt in to such use and disclosure).
Disclosure of Your
Information
Any personal
information provided by you will only be disclosed with your consent.  For example, when you list a vehicle, you
have the option of posting your email address.
If you choose not to, your email address will be kept confidential and
potential buyers can contact you through CarSavvy.com’s instant messaging
system.
If, as a Seller, you opt to
publish your email address or other contact information on the Site, you
acknowledge that such information will be available to any visitor to our Site.
As such, we cannot control how visitors will use your contact information.   For example, visitors may use your email
address to send you unsolicited emails that CarSavvy.com will not be able to
stop.   You should also remember that
your personal information will continue to be available on the Internet until
you delist your listing. You may discontinue your listing by delisting the
listing at CarSavvy.com
Amending Personal Information
As a visitor, you may also make
corrections or updates to the personal information that you provide us.  With respect to your personal contact
information, you make changes online.
When making changes online, simply click "Edit Listing" on the
CarSavvy.com home page, enter your Login and Password, click
"Login”.  Please note that this information will be located
on a secure site.
Use of Website Tracking and
Cookies
An Internet Protocol (“IP”)
address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer
whenever you are on the Internet. CarSavvy.com collects IP addresses for the
purposes of: helping us diagnose problems with our computers, for
administrative purposes, to report aggregated information, and to audit the use
of our Site.
Although, we do not link personal
information to your IP address, by using this Site, you acknowledge that we may
use IP addresses to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce
compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Site, visitors, or
others.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of
information that a website you visit sends to your computer for record-keeping
purposes.  Cookies are stored in a file
on your computer’s hard drive and are used to make your use of website simpler
for you by saving your preferences.
CarSavvy.com uses these preferences to make our Site more intuitive to
use when you return to the Site. Cookies do not identify you personally unless
you have chosen to provide personal information to us.
CarSavvy.com also uses third party third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this Site (not including your name, address, or other personal information) to provide advertisements on this Site, other sites and other media about goods and services that may be of interest to you..
In providing advertisements, a unique third party cookie may be placed on your browser. You may also get cookies from such advertisers if you use the links on our Site to reach their respective websites. CarSavvy.com does not control or have access to these cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.
Changes to this Policy
CarSavvy.com may be required to revise this Privacy
Policy from time to time and you agree that CarSavvy.com may do so at any
time, by updating this posting.
CarSavvy.com may revise this Privacy Policy by means of a notice on the
Site and you agree that such changes will take effect after the revised Privacy
Policy is posted on the Site. Continued use of the Site after such changes are
posted will signify your agreement to these revised terms.  You should visit this page periodically to
review this Privacy Policy.
Possible Future Uses of
Information
In the unlikely event that another
company acquires the assets of CarSavvy.com, information on our
visitors/Sellers would be among the transferred assets.
E-mail Communications
We collect and store your email
address from any communications that you may send to CarSavvy.com by clicking
on any of the email links. We may use your email address to communicate with
you, if your email indicates that a response to your inquiry is requested or to
address a concern or complaint you may have.
Whom can I contact for further
information?
If you wish to contact us to:
inquire about our privacy practices;
provide feedback and comments;
access or correct your personal information we
have; and/or
opt out of further communications, contact us as
detailed below.
Email: privacyofficer@CarSavvy.com
Links on CarSavvy.com
This site contains links to other
sites. CarSavvy.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the
content of such websites.
